See?
I never would've thought to do that.
(Sheldon:)Clearly I made a good choice
farming this out to you.
I'm telling you,
Amy hit the boyfriend jackpot.
(Sheldon:)Anyway...
(Sheldon:)...my socks are on.
Let's knock them off.
(Alex:)Well, um, I know
she loves playing the harp...
(Alex:)...so I found this beautiful music box
that plays one of her favorite songs.
(Sheldon:)Now, Amy already has a real harp...
(Sheldon:)...and it can play any song.
(Sheldon:)What are you trying to pull here?
- No, it's just I thought...
- Next.
(Alex:)Okay, um, I know she's a fan
of The Canterbury Tales...
(Leonard:)Mm.
(Alex:)...so I found this cool map that illustrates
the characters' journey through England.
(Alex:)We could put it in a really nice frame.
(Sheldon:)But she's got Google Maps on her phone.